Are you doing the football pools, Brain?
Brain,你正在下足球赛的赌注吗?
Yes, I've nearly finished, Julie.
是的.我就要弄完了,Julie.
I'm sure we'll win something this week.
我敢肯定这星期我们会赢点什么的.
You always say that, but we never win anything!
你老是那样说,但是我们从来没赢过!
What will you do if you win a lot of money?
要是你赢了许多钱,你会做什么呢?
If I win a lot of money I'll buy you a mink coat!
要是我赢了许多钱,我给你买件貂皮大衣.
I don't want a mink coat!
我不想要貂皮大衣.
I want to see the world.
我想去看看世界.
All right. If we win a lot of money,
好的.要是我们赢了很多钱,
We'll travel round the world and we'll stay at the best hotels.
我们就去周游世界,并且住最好的旅馆.
Then we'll return home and buy a big house in the country.
然后我们返回家园,在乡下买幢大房子.
We'll have a beautiful garden and ...
我们将有一个漂亮的花园和……
But if we spend all that money we'll be poor again.
但是如果我们把所有那些钱都花光了,我们又会变穷的.
What'll we do then?
那时我们怎么办呢?
If we spend all the money,we'll try and win the football pools again.
如果我们花光了所有钱,我们设法在足球赛赌注上再赢一次.
It's a pleasant dream but everything depends on 'if'!
这是个美好的梦,但一切都取决于“如果”!